{
    "name": ".\\GoogleACE\\Create and Manage Cloud Resources\\CreateRegionalLoadBalancer.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute forwarding-rules create www-rule --region us-east1 --ports 80 --address network-lb-ip-1 --target-pool www-pool",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1705334139.4859185,
            "question": "How would you add a forwarding rule called www-rule in region us-east1, on port 80, pointing at extnernal IP network-lb-ip-1 using target-pool www-pool?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "1. Create static IP 2. Create health check 3. Create target pool 4. Add instances to target pool 5. Add forwarding rule",
                "1. Create static ip 2. Create health check 3. Create target-pool 4. Add instances to target-pool 5. Create forwarding rule",
                "1. Create static ip address 2. create health check 3. create target-pool 4. Add instances to target pools 5. Add forwarding rule",
                "1. Create external IP 2. Create Health Check 3. Create Target-Pool 4. Add instances to Pool 5. Create forwarding rule"
            ],
            "answer": "1. Create a static external IP address 2. Add legacy HTTP health check 3. Add target pool 4. Add instances to pool 5. Add forwarding rule",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1705334409.0811539,
            "question": "What are the steps to configure a load balancing service?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute firewall-rules create www-firewall-network-lb --target-tags network-lb-tag --allow tcp:80"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute firewall-rules create www-firewall-network-lb --target-tags network-lb-tag --alow tcp:80",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1705334444.631935,
            "question": "How would you create a firewall rule called www-firewall-network-lb with tag network-lb-tag that allows TCP traffic on port 80?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute http-health-checks create basic-check",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1705334458.2651696,
            "question": "How would you create a legacy HTTP health check resource?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute addresses create network-lb-ip-1 --region us-east1",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705334065.2918398,
            "question": "How would you create a static external IP address for your load balancer called network-lb-ip-1 in region us-east1?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud config set compute/region us-east1",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705334148.734912,
            "question": "How would you set the default region to use-east1?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute target-pools add-instances www-pool --instances=www1,www2,www3"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute target-pools add-instances www-pool --instances www1, www2, www3",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1705334182.601865,
            "question": "How would you add instances [www1, www2, www3] to pool www-pool?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute instances list",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705334422.6898832,
            "question": "How would you list compute VM instance?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute target-pools create www-pool --region us-east1 --http-health-check basic-check",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705334695.0210402,
            "question": "How would you create a target pool called www-pool in region us-east1 with HTTP check basic-check?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "1. Create instance 2. Create firewall rule",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705334667.562585,
            "question": "What are the steps to create a web server instance?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "1. Configure region 2. Create instances 3. Create Load Balancer",
                "1. Create instances 2. Configure Load Balancer service"
            ],
            "answer": "1. Set default region and zone 2. Create web server instances 3. Configure load balancing service",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1705334546.3529592,
            "question": "What are the steps to create a regional load balancer?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud config set compute/zone us-east1-1",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1705334560.625613,
            "question": "How would you set the default zone to us-east1-1?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}